Guide to the Records of Graham Windham 1804-2011 MS 2916
New-York Historical Society
- Series III - Graham Windham, 1970-2011 (bulk 1977-2010), 11430
  - Subseries III.2 - Committee Minutes, 1982-2000, 11985
    - Executive Committee, 1998 April 23; 47948 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee, 1998 May 21; 47949 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee, 1998 June 24; 47950 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, 1998 August-October; 47951 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Committee, 1989-1993; 47952 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Committee, 1998-2000; 47953 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 9)
    - Finance Committee, 1982-1989; 47954 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee, 1990; 47955 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee, 1991; 47956 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee, 1992-1993; 47957 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee, 1996; 47958 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee, 1997 July 29; 47959 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee, 1997 July 29; 47960 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee, 1997 October 7; 47961 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee, 1997 November 11; 47962 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 5)
    - Finance Committee - Accounting procedures and auditor's report, 1997; 47963 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 6)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 February 12; 47964 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 7)
    - Special Finance Meeting, 1998 March 10; 47965 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 March 12; 47966 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 April 16; 47967 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 May 14; 47968 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 June 16; 47969 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 5)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 September 10; 47970 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 6)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 September-October; 47971 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 October 15; 47972 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 8)
    - Finance Committee, 1998 November 12; 47973 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 9)
    - Finance Committee, 1999 January 13; 47974 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee, 1999 February 11; 47975 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee, 1999 April 8; 47976 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee, 1999 June 8; 47977 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee, 1999 July 14; 47978 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 5)
    - Finance Committee, 1999 October 13; 47979 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 6)
    - Finance Committee, 2000 March 30; 47980 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee, 2000 June 7; 47981 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 8)
    - Executive Council, 1997 July 7; 47982 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 9)
    - Fund Development Committee, 1988-1994; 47983 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 1)
    - Fund Development Committee, 1997-1998; 47984 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 2)
    - Cultural/Recreational Committee, 1989; 47985 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 3)
    - Capital Campaign - Building Committee, 1989-1992; 47986 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 4)
    - Facilities Property Committee, 1992; 47987 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 5)
    - Board Program Committee, 1992-1993; 47988 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 6)
    - Development Committee, 1 of 2, 1990-1998; 47989 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 7)
    - Development Committee, 2 of 2, 1990-1998; 47990 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 8)
    - Development Committee, 1996; 47991 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 9)
    - Development Committee, 1997; 47992 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 10)
  - Subseries III.3 - Annual Reports, 1977-2006, 11983
    The subseries contains Graham Windham annual reports from 1977-2006. There are no annual reports for 1986-1988 or 2001-2002.
    The agency did not produce annual reports in 1986-1988; however, it distributed programs at the annual galas in those years incorporating some of the information that would typically be included in an annual report. For copies of gala programs, please see Subseries III.6 - Office of Development - Printed Matter.
    - Annual Report, 1977-1978; 50067 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, 1978-1979; 50068 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report, 1979-1980; 50069 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 1980-1981; 50070 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1981-1982; 50071 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports and President Reports, 1982-1985; 50072 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report, 1989; 50073 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1990; 50074 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1991; 50075 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1992; 50076 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, 1993; 50077 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, 1994; 50078 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, 1995; 50079 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, 1996; 50080 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report, 1997-1998; 50081 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 1999; 50082 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 2000; 50083 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 2003-2004; 50084 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report, 2004; 50085 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 2005-2006; 50086 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III.4 - Office of Joyce Lapenn, 1989-1996, 11499
    The subseries contains seven boxes of memoranda, reports, grant proposals, correspondence and related materials from the office of Graham Windham's President and Chief Executive Officer Joyce Lapenn, from 1989-1996. Folders are arranged topically, in the order in which they were arranged at Graham Windham. Records in this subseries are closed to the public for a period of 100 years from the date of their creation.
    - NYC Office of the Mayor, 1989-1993; 50093 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 1)
    - I.T.U. [Intensive Treatment Unit] Campus, 1994; 50094 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 2)
    - After School Program - Manhattan Center, 1992; 50095 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 3)
    - NYC ACP Headstart, 1993; 50096 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 4)
    - Literacy, 1991-1992; 50097 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 5)
    - Even Start Family Literacy Program, 1992; 50098 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 6)
    - NYS Even Start, 1993; 50099 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Referral Center request forms, 1992; 50100 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 8)
    - Volunteers - Individuals, 1991-1993; 50101 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activities - Parkside, 1993; 50102 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Office for Voluntary Service, 1992; 50103 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 11)
    - Volunteers - Campus Procedures, 1992; 50104 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activities, 1992; 50105 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 13)
    - Manual - Volunteers, 1991; 50106 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Orientation, 1991; 50107 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Opportunities, 1991; 50108 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Job Description, circa 1990-1995; 50109 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 4)
    - Volunteers - Miscellaneous including Friends, 1992-1993; 50110 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 5)
    - Children's Letters to Volunteers, 1995; 50111 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 6)
    - Board manual and GW History including OAS and Windham, 1989; 50112 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 7)
    - NYS Council on the Arts - Architecture, Planning, etc. re: Adaptive Use Study Plan, 1991; 50113 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 8)
    - Project SCDC Family Daycare, 1993-1994; 50114 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 1)
    - NYS Department of Health, 1995; 50115 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 2)
    - NYC DMHS [Dept. of Mental Health etc.] re: OAS and WCC - Includes certificate, 1995; 50116 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 3)
    - DMHS (2 of 2), 1995; 50117 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 4)
    - NYS Healthy Families, NYS Healthy Start Proposal, 1993; 50118 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 5)
    - NYS DSS [Dept. of Social Services] Minority Mentor Project, 1991; 50119 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 6)
    - Early Childhood FDC [Family Day Care] Development, 1993; 50120 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 7)
    - CWA [Child Welfare Administration] Prevention Services/Substance Abuse, 1 of 3 folders, 1990; 50121 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 1)
    - CWA [Child Welfare Administration] Prevention Services/Substance Abuse, 2 of 3 folders, 1990; 50122 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 2)
    - CWA [Child Welfare Administration] Prevention Services/Substance Abuse, 3 of 3 folders, 1990; 50123 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 3)
    - NYS D.S.A.S. [Division of Substance Abuse Services] 1992 re: 1993-94, 50124 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 4)
    - NYS Department of Health/AIDS Institution, 1993; 50125 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 5)
    - CWA [Child Welfare Administration] Therapeutic FBH, 1989; 50126 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 6)
    - NYS Department of Youth, 1992; 50127 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 7)
    - US DHHS [Dept. of Health and Human Services] Adoption cori/rpt/cont, 1 of 2 folders, 1989-1992; 50128 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 1)
    - US DHHS [Dept. of Health and Human Services] Adoption cori/rpt/cont, 2 of 2 folders, 1989-1992; 50129 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 2)
    - CWA [Child Welfare Administration] Adoption Recruitment, 1990-1992; 50130 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 3)
    - Post Legal Adoption (Federal), 1 of 3 folders, 1990 and 1994; 50131 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 4)
    - Post Legal Adoption (Federal), 2 of 3 folders, 1990 and 1994; 50132 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 5)
    - Post Legal Adoption (Federal), 3 of 3 folders, 1993; 50133 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 6)
    - Post Legal Adoption DHHS (Federal), 1995; 50134 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 7)
    - CWA Prevention Services/Substance Abuse, 1 of 4 folders, 1990-1991; 50135 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 1)
    - CWA Prevention Services/Substance Abuse, 2 of 4 folders, 1990; 50136 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 2)
    - CWA Prevention Services/Substance Abuse, 3 of 4 folders, 1990; 50137 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 3)
    - CWA Prevention Services/Substance Abuse, 4 of 4 folders, 1990-1992; 50138 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 4)
    - Office of the Mayor, 1989-1993; 50139 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 5)
    - New York Cares Day, 1992; 50140 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Recognition Luncheons, 1992-1993; 50141 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 2)
    - NYS ECIF: Project TLC: A Model Program for Family Child Care HUD Grant, 1996; 50142 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 3)
    - HUD Notes and Drafts, and Organizational Chart, 1996; 50143 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 4)
    - NYS Department of Mental Health re: Adam Clayton Powell Jr. Academy/Manhattan Center, 1996; 50144 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 5)
  - Subseries III.5 - Greenburgh-Graham Union Free School District, 1970-2009, 11501
    On July 1, 1967, the New York State Legislature established the Greenburgh-Graham Union Free School District on the campus of Graham School in Hastings-on-Hudson, New York, to provide specialized education to the children under its jurisdiction.
    The subseries consists of minutes and related materials of meetings of the Board of Education of the Greenburgh-Graham Union Free School District 1997-1999 and minutes and materials from the School Board Nominating Committee 1996-2001, and various materials from the Graham School 1970-2009, including printed materials and materials that were kept at the Graham School but are related to other programs.
    The School Board Nominating Committee minutes and related materials are arranged first, followed by the GGUFSD Board of Education meeting materials, in boxes 50-52. The Board of Education meeting materials had been bound in binders as board packets, marked with the name of Poul Jensen, Vice President of the Board. The original binders have been discarded, and all materials assembled in binders have been re-foldered in archival folders in the same arrangement. Most board packets include minutes of the previous meeting, an agenda for the upcoming meeting, and supplementary materials. Materials in boxes 50-52 are closed to the public for a period of 100 years from the date of their creation.
    The subseries also contains mixed materials (mainly printed matter) from the school including school newsletters 1974-1986 and 2008-2009; examples of student work from the 1970's; a brochure, staff handbooks, invitations and other printed material; and clippings and articles, all in Box 53. Box 54 contains other administrative materials related to the school, as well as to other programs of Graham-Windham and the agency in general. These materials include procedural instructions, newsletters, and informational materials. They have been kept in original order.
    The subseries concludes with school yearbooks 1989-2008.
    Additional pre-1977 school brochures may be found in Series 1.8 - printed matter, while other brochures from after the 1977 merger may be found in Series III.6 - development department printed matter.
    - School Board Nominating Committee, 1995 September - 1997 January; 50227 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 1)
    - GGUFSD Board of Ed, 1997 March-May; 50228 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 2)
    - Nominating Committee Including School Board, 1999; 50229 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 3)
    - Nominating Committee Including School Board, 2001; 50230 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 4)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1997 June; 50231 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 5)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1997 August; 50232 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 6)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1997 September; 50233 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 7)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1997 September-October; 50234 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 8)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1997 November; 50241 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 1)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1997 December; 50242 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 2)
    - School District Financial Statements and Auditors' Report, 1997 December; 50243 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 3)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1998 January; 50244 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 4)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1998 February; 50245 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 5)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1998 March; 50246 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 6)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1998 April; 50247 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 7)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1998 May; 50248 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 1)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1998 September; 50249 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 2)
    - Long Range Instructional Technology Plan, 1998 September 23; 50250 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 3)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1999 January; 50251 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 4)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1999 March; 50252 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 5)
    - GGUFSD Board of Education Meeting Materials, 1999 June; 50253 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 6)
    - Graham School songs, poems by students, circa 1970 and undated; 50254 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 1)
    - The Graham Reporter - school newsletter, circa 1974-1986; 50255 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 2)
    - Booklet on the GGUFSD, circa 1977-1979; 50256 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 3)
    - Graham School Variety Show Program, 1978; 50257 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 4)
    - Booklets of poems written by Graham-Windham school children, 1984-1985; 50258 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 5)
    - GGUFSD staff handbook, 1988; 50259 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 6)
    - Invitation to groundbreaking, 1991 April; 50260 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 7)
    - Westchester School/Business Partnerships reception program, 1991 October; 50261 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 8)
    - Elementary/Intermediate School staff handbook, circa 1997 August; 50262 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 9)
    - Graham School newsletter, 2008-2009; 50263 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 10)
    - The Journal News re: The Tigers, 2008 December; 50264 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 11)
    - The Journal News re: Work 2 Workout, 2008 December; 50265 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 12)
    - The Journal News re: Work 2 Workout, 2009 January; 50266 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 13)
    - The Journal News re: the Tigers, 2009 March; 50267 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 14)
    - The Journal News re: Teach for America, 2009 July; 50268 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 15)
    - NY Nonprofit Press re: Jess Danhauser, 2009 November; 50269 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 16)
    - The Rivertowns Enterprise re: Teach for America and Make a Difference Day, 2009 October-November; 50270 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 17)
    - Article re: Graham School, undated; 50271 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 18)
    - Articles re: Graham School, 1985-1994 and undated; 50272 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 19)
    - Partial Table of Organization, undated; 50273 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 1)
    - Graham-Windham newsletters, 1984-1986; 50274 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 2)
    - Graham-Windham fact sheets, 1986; 50275 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 3)
    - Graham-Windham frequently asked questions, circa 1990s; 50276 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 4)
    - Clinical privileges for assisting occupational, art, and recreation therapists, circa 1980s; 50277 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 5)
    - How to do evaluations, circa 1980s; 50278 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 6)
    - Graham-Windham Manhattan Center Outpatient Child and Adolescent Mental Health Program, 1980; 50279 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 7)
    - Uniform Case Records, 1981; 50280 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 8)
    - Guidelines to compliance with outpatient program regulations (mental health), 1982; 50281 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 9)
    - Roleplaying instructions for interviews, 1983; 50282 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 10)
    - Leadership development profile seminar, 1983; 50283 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 11)
    - Bureau of Utilization review, 1985; 50284 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 12)
    - Departmental Goals and Objective form, 1987; 50285 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 13)
    - Map of GW campus and program for afternoon at campus, undated; 50286 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 14)
    - Manhattan Mental Health Center, undated; 50287 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 15)
    - How to use charts and posters, circa 1980s; 50288 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 16)
    - Ottilie Home for Children by-laws and rules and regulations, 1983; 50289 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 17)
    - Ottilie Home for Children intake criteria, circa 1980s; 50290 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 18)
    - Residential Treatment Center and school miscellaneous, 1995; 50291 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 19)
    - Graham Elementary/Middle School Yearbooks, 2002-2004; 50292 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 20)
    - Graham Elementary/Middle School Yearbooks, 2005-2006; 50293 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 21)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 1989; 50294 (Volume 195)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 1989; 50295 (Volume 196)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 1993; 50296 (Volume 197)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 1993; 50297 (Volume 198)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 1994; 50298 (Volume 199)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 1999; 50299 (Volume 200)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 2000; 50300 (Volume 201)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 2000; 50301 (Volume 202)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 2001; 50302 (Volume 203)
    - GGUFSD High School Yearbook, 2003; 50303 (Volume 204)
    - GGUFSD High School Yearbook, 2004; 50304 (Volume 205)
    - GGUFSD High School Yearbook, 2004; 50305 (Volume 206)
    - GGUFSD High School Yearbook, 2005; 50306 (Volume 207)
    - GGUFSD High School Yearbook, 2005; 50307 (Volume 208)
    - GGUFSD High School Yearbook, 2006; 50308 (Volume 209)
    - GGUFSD High School Yearbook, 2006; 50309 (Volume 210)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 2007; 50310 (Volume 211)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 2007; 50311 (Volume 212)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 2007; 50312 (Volume 213)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 2008; 50313 (Volume 214)
    - GGUFSD School Yearbook, 2008; 50314 (Volume 215)
  - Subseries III.6 - Office of Development - Printed Matter, circa 1977-2011, 11500
    The Office of Development at Graham Windham is responsible for all fundraising and public relations. Material from the department has been subdivided into four subseries (III.6-9) based on material type. Printed materials produced and/or collected by the Office of Development have been arranged as subseries III.6.
    A few folders in the subseries include memos, notes, or correspondence related to the printed matter; however, most memos, notes, reports, correspondence and other administrative material of the Development Department is arranged in subseries III.7.
    Materials in Subseries III.6 are arranged by type in the following order: event programs and invitations 1986-2010; informational and fundraising pamphlets, brochures, fliers, advertisements and miscellaneous printed matter 1980-2006 and undated; alumni newsletters 1994-1997; employee newsletters 1994-1996; newsletters for the general public 1983-2011.
    - Gala Program and Invitation, 1986; 50417 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 1)
    - Isabella Graham Award Programs, 1986 and 1988; 50418 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 2)
    - Gala Program, 1987; 50419 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 3)
    - Gala Program and Invitation, 1988; 50420 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 4)
    - Gala Program and Invitation, 1991; 50421 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 5)
    - "Classic Black" Benefit, 1991; 50422 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Event Invitations, 1991-1994; 50423 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 7)
    - Gala Program and Invitation, 1992; 50424 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Gala Invitations, circa 1993-2003; 50425 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 9)
    - Gala Program, 1994; 50426 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 10)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Opening and Halloween Benefit Skating Party, 1994 June and October; 50700 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 11)
    - Gala Program, 1995; 50427 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 12)
    - Save the Date Card, 190th Anniversary, 1996; 50428 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 13)
    - Gala Program, 1996; 50429 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 14)
    - Gala Program and Invitation, 1997; 50430 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 15)
    - Gala, 1998; 50431 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 16)
    - Wine Tasting Event, 1998; 50432 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 17)
    - Gala Invitation, 1999; 50433 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 1)
    - Gala Program, 2000; 50434 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 2)
    - Gala, 2001; 50435 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 3)
    - Gala Program, 2005; 50436 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 4)
    - Bicentennial Ball, 2006; 50437 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 5)
    - Gala Program and Invitation, 2007; 50438 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 6)
    - Elizabeth Hamilton Award Luncheon Programs and Invitation, 2007; 50439 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 7)
    - Annual Award Luncheon, 2009; 50440 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 8)
    - Leadership Council Gala, 2010; 50441 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 9)
    - Foster Care Pamphlet: "Scott needs your home", circa 1980; 50442 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 10)
    - 175th Anniversary Brochure, 1980-1981; 50443 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 11)
    - Fundraising Fliers: "For the Good of All", 1983; 50444 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 12)
    - Caseworker Booklet, 1986; 50445 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 13)
    - Printed Matter, 1987; 50446 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Matter, circa 1980-1989; 50447 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 15)
    - "Every Child Deserves a Future" pamphlets (English and Spanish), circa 1988; 50448 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 16)
    - "Business is Booming" fundraising ad, circa 1989; 50449 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 1)
    - "Our Children, Our Future" pamphlets, English and Spanish, circa 1990; 50450 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 2)
    - "Now More Than Ever Before" fundraising pamphlet, circa 1990-1992; 50451 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous leaflets, 1990; 50452 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 4)
    - Campus School Miscellaneous printed matter, 1991-1992; 50453 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 5)
    - Community School District Five Superintendent's Report, 1991-1992; 50454 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 6)